questions = {
    'Chemistry': [
        {'question' : 'What is the coordination number of cobalt in the complex [Co(NH₃)₆]³⁺?', 'answers' : ['6', '12', '4', '8'], 'correct' : '6'},
        {'question' : 'What is the primary intermolecular force present in liquid HF (hydrofluoric acid)?', 'answers' : ['Van der Waals forces', 'Dipole-dipole interactions', 'London dispersion forces', 'Hydrogen bonding'], 'correct' : 'Hydrogen bonding'},
        {'question' : 'What is the hybridization of the central atom in sulfur hexafluoride (SF₆)?', 'answers' : ['sp³', 'sp³d²', 'sp²d', 'sp³d'], 'correct' : 'sp³d²'},
        {'question' : 'Which element has the highest electron affinity?', 'answers' : ['Fluorine (F)', 'Oxygen (O)', 'Chlorine (Cl)', 'Bromine (Br)'], 'correct' : 'Chlorine (Cl)'},
        {'question' : 'In organic chemistry, what is the main product formed when 2-butanol undergoes dehydration?', 'answers' : ['1-butene', 'Butanol', '2-butanone', '2-butene'], 'correct' : '2-butene'},
        {'question' : 'Which of the following amino acids has a sulfur atom in its side chain?', 'answers' : ['Lysine', 'Cysteine', 'Valine', 'Glycine'], 'correct' : 'Cysteine'},
        {'question' : 'What is the IUPAC name for acetone?', 'answers' : ['Propan-2-one', 'Propanal', '2-Propanol', 'Methanone'], 'correct' : 'Propan-2-one'},
        {'question' : 'In an SN2 reaction mechanism, what is the stereochemical outcome at the reaction site?', 'answers' : ['Retention of configuration', 'Racemization', 'No change in configuration', 'Inversion of configuration'], 'correct' : 'Inversion of configuration'},
        {'question' : 'What is the molecular geometry of XeF₄?', 'answers' : ['Trigonal bipyramidal', 'Octahedral', 'Square planar', 'Tetrahedral'], 'correct' : 'Square planar'},
        {'question' : 'Which gas law best describes the relationship between pressure and temperature at constant volume?', 'answers' : ["Boyle’s Law", "Gay-Lussac’s Law", "Charles’s Law", "Avogadro’s Law"], 'correct' : "Gay-Lussac’s Law"}
    ]
}
